♪ In the not‐too‐distant
future ♪
♪ next Sunday, a, d, ♪
♪ there was a guy
named Joel ♪
♪ not too different
from you or me ♪
♪ he worked
at gizmonic institute ♪
♪ just another face
in a red jumpsuit ♪
♪ he did a good job
cleaning up the place ♪
♪ but his bosses
didn't like him ♪
♪ so they shot him
into space ♪
♪ we'll send him
cheesy movies ♪
♪ the worst we can find,
la‐la‐la ♪
♪ he'll have to sit
and watch them all ♪
♪ and we'll monitor his mind,
la‐la‐la ♪
♪ now, keep in mind
Joel can't control ♪
♪ when the movies
begin or end, la‐la‐la ♪
♪ because he used
those special parts ♪
♪ to make his robot friends ♪
♪ robot roll call ♪
‐ ♪ cambot ♪
‐ pan left,
‐ ♪ gypsy ♪
‐ hi, girl,
‐ ♪ Tom servo ♪
‐ what a cool guy,
‐ ♪ cro‐o‐o‐ow ♪
‐ wisecracker,
♪ if you're wondering
how he eats and breathes ♪
♪ and other science facts,
la‐la‐la ♪
♪ repeat to yourself,
"it's just a show" ♪
♪ "I should really
just relax" ♪
♪ for mystery science
theater 3000 ♪
Computeroice:
30 seconds to
commercial sign,
hey, everybody, I'm Joel,
I'm marooned in outer space
on the satellite of love,
and I'm the subject of
a bizarre movie‐watching
experiment,
now, I guess, so are you,
I'm up here with
my two homemade buddies‐‐
crow and Tom servo here,
yeah,
and we're working
on Tom servo now,
I think, uh‐‐
trying to fix him up,
hey, watch what
you're doing there,
it's the only torso I have,
commercial sign
in 15 seconds,
well, I think I found
the problem here, buddy,
some kind of a computer virus
happening here,
oh, grody, it looks like
a magnetic tapeworm,
commercial sign
in 5, 4, 3, 2,,,
commercial sign now,
I got it, you'll be
shipshape in no time,
we'll be right back,
don't go away,
you'll be real gone,
♪
All right, that ought to
do it, buddy,
hop down and grab yourself
a lollipop,
I feel like a new man,
I don't know what you did,
but my back hasn't felt
this good in months,
cookin' with crisco now,
funny, you don't look
any better,
uh‐oh, you guys,
look downcast,
the big cheeses
are calling,
come in, Joel the mole,
my little frosted
sponge cake,
hey, sirs, what are you
wrecking today?
Oh, nothing, really,
we're just kind of
hanging out, you know‐‐
Larry, it's magic time,
make with the invention
exchange, plebe,
well, as you know,
even avid smokers
can't stand the smell
of a tar‐belching pipe,
and so I invented this‐‐
the never‐light pipe,
it's got a sophisticated
sprinkler system,
built in with
a smoke detector,
so any time somebody
tries to light up,,,
see, it puts it out for you,
‐ I'll try it on him,
‐ ouch,
like that, they should never,
ever be able to light up
with this thing,
no more,
it's not supposed to work,
oh!
Well, what do you
think, sirs?
I think it's
almost as clever
as the prince Albert
in a can gag,
I love that gag!
It's great!
Better let him out,
he'll suffocate,
(aughs
now, get ready
for our part,
Larry, Larry?
Now, lar and I have
discovered
that children adore putting
things in their mouth,
and they love puppets,
we've combined the two,
put a little spin on it,
we call it "tongue puppets",
the show, Larry?
Hey, everybody, it's me‐‐
mr, stinky,
oh, love everybody here,
(umbling )
Ha ha ha! Ye,
I think you might
win the award
for the most
unsanitary toy,
‐ well, thank you,
‐ thank you very much,
‐ congratulations,
‐ absolutely, nice job,
all:H, brother,
we finally got one,
it's about time,
it's great,
oh, heh heh,
your film today, Joel,
is a little teen
exploitation film
called untamed youth,
and, well, it stars
the grande dame
of pimply teenage romps,
the queen of
adolescent angst‐‐
‐ mamie Van hooter,
‐ Van doren,
doren, mamie Van doren,
it's got hep cats,
cool chicks,
insensitive
authority figures
and few show‐stopping
production numbers,
enjoy,,,if you can,
‐ (larmuzzing
‐ oh, we got movies!
Let's go!
Those scientists
are just geeks,
at least it's
a Warner Bros, picture,
it sounds like it's
gonna be one of those
teen‐sploitation things,
hey, I hope
it's a cartoon first,
♪
Anytown, u, s, a,
Looks like he's
playing football
against Claude rains
university,
♪
How much you wanna bet
the word "daddy‐o"
is in this film
a million times?
Hey, after him! He's hiding
behind those credits,
I think hiding from the police
would be easier
if this was before
harvest time,
at least you had some corn,
you know?
I think there's gonna be
a lot of corn in this,
this is like
the Stephen King book‐‐
children of the dirt,
hey, hide, quick,
he's roadkill,
look at that,
don't ever play chicken
with two cop cars,
can't win,
thought you could hide
behind the credits, huh?
Heh,
works every time,
so he stole an onion,
what are you gonna do?
Is that the primordial soup?
Hey, there's a girl in my soup,
heh heh!
Don't worry,
she won't eat much,
(orcedaughter
okay, come on out!
Well, you go away first!
Oh, that'd be
neglect of duty,
well, at least they're
not unbathed youths,
you're not much
of a gentleman,
it's the maytag repairman,
he does look lonely,
now get out!
Hiya, Mitch!
Oh, hi, landis,
whatcha doin'? Fishing?
No, just sexually
harassing a few teens,
they're swimming
with their high heels on,
you stick to your
cotton‐picking,
my cotton‐picking what?
Nice tag,
Oh, good, I thought they were
gonna put their luggage on,
huh? Hat?
So, I understand
you two are untamed,
How old are you two?
22,
36,
21,
that's my locker
combination,
where do you live?
Du quoin,
du what?
Du quoin, Illinois,
the biggest county fair
in the country,
sulky races and everything,
home of the fighting ducks
and the glass‐bottom boats,
striptease?
No, thank you,
,,,dances, skits‐‐
don't bother briefing him,
where were you going?
To l, a,
what do you mean, "were"?
Just that,
pick up your stuff,
you‐‐you mean
you'd take us in
just for swimming around
in that pond?
We were so hot,
we walked for miles,
she's still hot,
hitchhiking's also against
the county code,
now, pick up that stuff
and let's go,
what a grouch,
♪
There's no room
for our stuff,
the back seat's filled
with a jazz combo,
no, no, baggage in the back,
you in front,
now, you drive it into town
and I'll meet you there,
quit playing that sax,
meanwhile,
at mount Vernon,,,
hitchhiking may not seem
a serious offense to you,
but there have been
two murders
involving hitchhiking
in the last seven months,
and I committed
both of them,
in one case,
a hitchhiker killed a man
for his car and money,
just for snoring too loud,
,,, was assaulted
and murdered,
her name was pina,
,,, without visible means
of support,
oh, I wouldn't say that,
you have pled guilty,
I know sentence you,,,
to death?
Jane lowe,
and you, penny lowe,
to 30 days' confinement,
huh?
Now, that may seem
harsh to you,
'cause it is,
but I'm going
to give you a choice,
you may serve your sentence
in the county jail,
or you may serve it
as agricultural workers
on a ranch,
green acres?
Jail, please, jail,
you will do healthy,
outdoor work,
for which
you will be paid,
they look healthy enough,
and you will regain
your self‐respect,
we never lost it,
your honor,
what about this movie?
Real stoic judge,
they call her "stone‐face",
( indistinct )
We'll take the healthy
outdoor work, ma'am,
so decreed,
like I care,
Mitch? Oh, Bob!
What a wonderful surprise!
Not very judge‐like,
so good to see you,
I've got a thousand
things to tell you,
oh, excuse me a minute,
court's adjourned
until tomorrow morning,
then there's gonna be
a big party,
hmm, big deal,
with her for a mom,
that guy's got
a life sentence,
all right, come on,
right out the door,
kooky teeners,
Any‐really‐groovy‐city,
u, s, a,
looks like Tom waits'
hometown,
tire farming,
it's hard, but it's worth it,
somewhere out there
is the ark of the covenant,
in a radio,
oh, I hope it's not
the Von tropp family,
I hate them,
Hey, it's the body snatcher
pod wagon,
( indistinct chatter )
Looks like one of
those clown cars,
it is a clown car,
come on, hurry up,
get a move on,
they just keep piling out,
Lou gossett, Jr,
will be out here
to chat with you
a little later,
( indistinct )
Ah, the original cast
of the dirty dozen,
,,,in your case,
cotton picking‐‐
is not to exceed $2,50 a day
for each day,
and that's before tax,
so the code goes on
to say,
"the net credits
to each convict's account
shall not be permitted
to exceed 75 cents a day,"
that's your take‐home pay,
cubby!
Gregor,
Annette,
hoppy,
Mabel,
and Mabel,
now, that means if any
of you monkeys escapes,
enough dough will be taken
from the daily pay,,,
monkey dough?
,,,$200 for the reward,
and if you land
on free parking,
you get it back,
which is great,
just figure you're
on an honor farm,
you can grown honor
like that?
Some more crows to follow
the big red machine,
what the hell
does that mean?
Looks like his hat
is welded to his head,
why'd you have to call us
"convicts" us for, mister?
You pick 400 pounds a day,
I'll call you cotton pickers,
say, I like that,
hey, you,
quit hoppin' around,
how old are you, baby?
19,
how did you know
to call me that?
'Cause of the feet
in your pajamas,
that's what everybody
calls me‐‐baby,
( laughs )
I should think so,
you'll be perfect
for my experiments,
hmm, bookends,
we're sisters,
oh, wow,
how did they tangle
with the law?
Hitchhiking vags,
we're not vagrants,
we're on our way to l, a,
for a booking,
we're entertainers,
oh, yeah, I bet,
that's what this place
needs‐‐entertainment,
I myself dabble
in ventriloquism,
will you stop bouncing around
back there?
,,,these people squared away,
show them where to sleep
and sell them
some work clothes,
all right, kids,
follow me,
♪
Killer sax, man,
Just kids,
yeah, but watch it,
well, here's to
cotton pickin',,,
and little gal
cotton pickers,
shut up,
let's see‐‐
20 bucks a head,
that's 140 you owe me,
I know, I know,
I have that much
in my skin,
this goes right into
a new t, v, set for the wife,
why don't you
put it in a bank?
Hush, paws,
come with daddy,
♪
‐ Jackson,
‐ yes, sir,
hey, little man,
come here,
huh?
What were you doing
in the house?
Just bringing in today's
tallies, mr, tropp,
you look real pretty
in lipstick,
works every time,
you've got 15 minutes
to get off of this place,
but, mr, tropp‐‐
get your pay and get lost!
Am I the sultriest person
you've ever seen
in your whole entire life?
Whoops!
( Turns music off )
( Turns vacuum on )
Fran, I'm home,
oh, it's you,
( Vacuum turns off )
Uh, you missed a spot,
what's the matter, honey?
I'm not finished yet,
yes, you are finished,
you just washed yourself out
of a housekeeper's job,
why, Ross,
what in the world‐‐
I warned you about
chintzing around,
I warned you
about that guy Jackson,
I told you that
that was the last time
I was gonna warn you,
now, get your clothes
and get out,
but I'm wearing
my clothes,
oh, no, Russ, please,
I'm sorry, honey,
I promise you I'll be good,
please, Russ,
I've worked hard for you!
I've done everything
I could,,,
say, she is Fran,
don't do any talking,,,
or bragging,
or spend the rest of your
time in the county clink,
hogan!
,,,male or female,
now get out of here,
♪ get to feeling like
a rolling stone ♪
♪ haven't got a place
to call my own,,, ♪
What are those?
♪ And the time has flown ♪
♪ rolling ♪
♪ like a rolling stone,,, ♪
That guitar makes
amazing sounds,
‐ hey, look! Greg Brady!
‐ Greg Brady!
♪ ,,, and the tears
I've known ♪
♪ rolling ♪
♪ like a rolling stone ♪
♪ knocking around ♪
Check out the lever action,
nice fulcrum,
you can see a lot of
chorus from here,
you know,
it really makes me miss
the potato and cotton fields
of earth,
hey, it's
blond lemon Jefferson,
(huckles
♪ never be alone,,, ♪
Anyone want a snow cone?
I could go to the galley,
no, thanks,
♪ get to feeling
like a rolling stone,,, ♪
Dig in, babe,
♪ haven't got a place
to call my own ♪
Ah, well, the show's
already started,
but I can seat you
up front,
♪ and the time has flown ♪
♪ oh, rolling ♪
♪ like a rolling‐‐ ♪
Uh, ix‐nay on the ump‐bay
and rind‐gay,
get out of here,
you peeper!
All: Tell him, Greg!
This is looking
like the reunion show
Greg's back from Sweden,
and he looks way different,
this is my bed,
what do you mean?
This is where they put me,
it was mine before,
we're sisters,
and we're staying together,
I don't care
if you're siamese twins,
catfight!
,,,you big trollop,
trollop fight,
"trollop", my dear,
means a soiled dove,
a fallen angel,
to put it sweet and neat,,,
hey, it's Lenny and squiggy
school,
you take that back,
or take a beating,
take the beating!
Come on, if you want
an Italian haircut,
huh?
Extra mousse or something,
I don't know,
break her neck,
oh, break her neck!
Greg, buddy, it's me‐‐
Tom! Tom servo!
( All shouting )
Scratch her eyes out,
( shouting continues )
Kill her! Kill her!
Fight her! Fight her!
Scratch her!
( Shouting continues )
( Screaming )
Oh, right in the eyehole,
oh, he's blind,
that's real funny,
real good, Greg,
( shouting continues )
All right,
I'll break it up,
oh, sorry, excuse me,
who's the big winner?
I got winner,
come on, I'm ready,
go ahead, hit me
in the mouth again,
you'll break
my dental plate,
this what you call
entertainment?
Well, you missed
the big cossack number,
you take a different bed
or a broken plate,
‐ now, what do you say?
‐ I say uncle,
I say aunt,
I say wow, ha ha!
I advise you two to save
your energy for the fields,
you hurt?
You?
I don't know what
he expects from them,
they're untamed,
all right, kids,
get dressed,
everybody to chow,
now, what was this catfight
all about?
Don't call me a cat,
meow,
I asked a question,
‐ it was over my bed,
‐ it was not‐‐
over your bed body,
(aughter
remember what I told you,
lillibet,
you're halfway back
to the pokey right now,
what about the gumby?
Cotton‐picking creep,
oh, save your energy,
he's all business,
yeah, all kinds,,,
including shady,
fishy, funny,,,
dopey, sneezy, grumpy,
did I get them all?
You missed a few,
but that's okay,
you're too tough for me,
oh, we gotta
get out of here,
let's go eat
at the mess hall, huh?
Would you like that?
Wait a minute!
I gotta get dressed!
‐ are you ready,
you guys?
‐ ready,
okay, today we'd like
to present our pageant‐‐
Greg Brady:
An American legacy,
(umming
Greg Brady, the eldest
of Mike Brady's three boys,
began his public life
at the age of 14,
when his widower father
married widow Carol,
who was bringing up
three very lovely girls,
he lived with
his large family
in a very spacious
split‐level house
in a Los Angeles suburb,
he attended Warren g, Harding
high school,
where he was
considered dreamy,
life wasn't all peaches
and cream for Greg Brady,
the pressures
of a huge step‐family
often caused things
to go wrong,
sharing a bedroom
with two bedrooms
would cramp Greg's style,
he later proceeded
to move into the den
and made it very mod,
(Umming
he wasn't ready
for the den life,
so he moved back to the
security of his brothers' room,
but again, he felt crowded,
and he eventually settled
in the attic,
the attic was good for Greg,
there, he blossomed
into a man,
nurturing his
singing career,
just trying to forget
the troubles of growing up,
like the time his hair
got turned orange,
or when Bobby left
his jumping frog
in the back of Greg's car
when he had a date,
oh, the carnage,
anyway, but that was
his past life,
life was good now,
in 1971,
Greg was receiving
6,500 fan letters a week,
that, and his studies
at Harding high,
kept Greg busy,
(Umming
but in 1974, Greg was faced
with the biggest shock
of his life,
his family was canceled,
without a primetime audience,
Greg's world began to crumble,
there were attempts
to revive his family,
but none succeeded,
he had hit rock‐bottom,
Greg couldn't even get
a suite on the love boat,
Brady lunch box in hand,
Greg headed for New York,
musical theater would
give him a last chance,
he appeared in the Broadway
production of pippin,
but then disappeared,
(Umming
it seemed america
had lost Greg Brady,
he was nowhere to be found,
until Christmas, 1988,
Greg was found
at a hospital in California,
it was him!
It was dr, Greg Brady!
He had become a doctor,,,
Greg Brady,
he returned
to his boyhood home
with his entire family,
and a very Brady Christmas
was had by all,
thank you, what?
Greg Brady, we on
the satellite of love
salute you,
you're one of
the good ones,
thank you, Greg,
you are groovy,
(umming
♪
Good pageant,
yeah, I thought
it was pretty good,
a tribute
to someone I love,
hey, it's evel knievel,
( rooster crows )
What you got, buster?
Telegram?
All right,
‐ mr, tropp?
‐ right,
Bob Steele,
hi, I'm rod iron,
how are you?
Glad to meet you,
say, you sure
look like her,
thanks,
I'm taking steroids,
‐ haven't forgotten how?
‐ no, I can run one,
good, you're on
the payroll as of now,
regular rate,
and glad to have you,
now, I don't know if you're
into weird scenes or not,
but check this thing out,
how's the place
look to you?
Swell, gee, you really
have it fixed up,
I really like your dirt,
makes money, though,
the easiest part
was getting your mother
to sell out to me,
she does that a lot,
she wrote me in formosa
she was gonna sell out,
landis!
That's Gladys?
But I was just goin'
to the store,
Bob Steele,
this is Jack landis,
Bob's gonna take over
your job,
I want you to handle
the field crew on "q" ranch,
I'll go get my gear,
oh, great,
first guy I meet hates me,
or you can eat with the crew
down at the mess hall,
okay,
landis,,,come here,
salad oil?
Get rid of that,
I'll drink it,
that's no way to pack
a reserve chute,
,,,you'll be off of here
in five minutes,
go join your crew,
okay, kid, on your way,
( starts engine )
Man, that kid sure looks good
up on that combine,
put some spurs on him,
make him sing show tunes,
he'll fit in real fine,
nature's rich bounty,
corn, soya bean, sorghum,,,
(Ndistinct )
Mining, agriculture
and untamed youth
forging an untamed land,
eating their weight
in cotton,
men naked
from the waist‐up,
watching days of our lives
day after day,
this is their story‐‐
the Valiant few
who dared to be different,
who dared to dream,
monster cars patrolling
the highways and byways,
radio announcer:
But, in spite of
this bumper crop,
prices may continue
to rise,
why? Because of the acute
shortage of labor
in many parts
of the southwest,
hey, he's got
a car payphone,
howdy, mr, tropp,
hiya,
(mitates horn honking )
I love that game,
mr, yancey,
mr, collingwood,
well, mr, tropp,
looks like you're
gonna have your crop
picked clean and bailed
in short order,
we just happened to notice,
going by your fields‐‐
you got plenty of hands
working for you,
two per person,
hard crops are ready
and ripe,
soon they'll be rotten,
rotten cotton,
you said you get us labor
to pick our fields,
that's right, I take 60%
of your harvest, you get 40,
now, wait a minute,
mr, tropp, you said‐‐
50‐50, you said,
look, fellas,
you took my time,
I've been talking to you
about this for two weeks,
that's the deal,
I get the labor,
you push me around
in a wheelbarrow
dressed as one of
the honeymooners,
your choice, pal,
but I'll be needing
over 100 hands,
200 for me,
where'll you get 'em?
Where will we get
the wheelbarrow?
You need 300 pickers?
All right, I'll get 'em,
that's my problem,
but that's not the question,
the thing is,,,
do you take the deal?
What can I do?
I don't like it,
but I'll take it,
uh, sorry about
my friend back there,
he's kind of a hothead,
let's find a way
to squeeze him out, huh?
It's tears for fears,
watch it there,
will you, boys?
Indiana bones,
we don't want leaves
and stems,
no, you just want
something for nothing,
you're asking for
a beltin' now, Billy,
I think they look like
the pet shop boys,
you're lookin'
for a workout, huh?
Yeah, do you have nautilus
or free weights?
Body by Bob Denver,
in the bailing shed,
now, there's a woman
outstanding in her field,
‐ (orced laughter )
‐ good one,
I'll never wear anything
made of cotton again,
oh, we gotta get us some
jeans and some flat shoes,
‐ what with?
‐ we got credit,
remember what the man said?
30 days of this, and‐‐
28 starting tomorrow,
chihuahua, there goes
another fingernail,
yeah, now that
you bit it off,
come on, guys,
we can help them,
stupidest crook in the world,
he steals cotton,
♪ oh, you ain't gonna make ♪
♪ a cotton picker out of me ♪
♪ bom‐bom‐bom,,, ♪
Shut up,
don't even start,
you know, the acoustics
in that cotton patch
are fantastic,
they sure aren't gonna make
a singer out of him,
♪ oh, you ain't gonna make ♪
♪ a cotton picker
out of me,,, ♪
That popcorn's enormous
out there,
Elvis has left
the cotton field,
hey, get me‐‐
I'm santy claus,
ha ha ha!
Look at that, must get
real lonely in the fields,
hey, look, way in the back‐‐
it's Eli Whitney,
just kidding,
♪ ,,,cotton picker
out of me,,, ♪
Fortunately, he's got
guitar strings
embedded across his chest,
‐ gilligan!
‐ skipper!
Mary Ann, ginger,
which one of those two
have rhythm?
I can't tell,
hey, stop playing
your sternum,
♪ makin' me laugh,
makin' me cry ♪
♪ makin' me roll, roll,
roll till I die,,, ♪
Strange alliances are made
in a hot cotton field,
♪ no, you ain't gonna make ♪
♪ a cotton picker
out of me,,, ♪
You know,
there's girls there,
see?
♪ A cotton picker
out of me ♪
♪ bom‐bom‐bom ♪
♪ you can make me poor,
make me rich ♪
♪ make me want
the seven‐year itch,,, ♪
Yikes!
There's a lot of rhythm
in this scene,
makes room for no acting,
♪ a cotton picker
out of me ♪
♪ bom‐bom‐bom,,, ♪
This is sort of like
up with people in prison,
♪ bom‐bom‐bom ♪
♪ you can make me sing,
or make me dance ♪
♪ make me rock
right out of my pants,,, ♪
‐ yikes,
‐ eww,
you know,
interesting enough,
this scene was included
in the film
scared straight!
What key is that in?
I like doing that
to the kids,
(rumbling
hey, it looks like he's driving
the swamp from mash,
What's the matter?
Ohh, I'm dizzy,
it's so hot,
the poppies made her sleep,
what's the matter with her?
Too much sun,
she's too hot,
I've got to get her
in the shade,
she ate too much cotton,
ohh,
it's okay,
( moaning )
Hey, nice field boots,
look, the field's
chock‐full of them,
boys, too,
she almost passed out,
too much sun,
let's get her in the shade,
open the door,
well, come on!
Uh‐uh,
now roll the windows up,
here, take some,
uh, wait,
that's my motorman's helper,
thanks, I'll be all right,
I'll sit and stay here
for a while,
you'd better get back
on the job,
and I'll start pounding
corn liquor,
‐ afraid of the boss,
huh, landis?
‐ not at all,
unless he's doing
his spooky face,
she might need a doctor,
I'll handle it,
I'm in charge of this crew,
I'm a barber,
they used to be doctors,
well, since no one has
any more lines here,
let's just, uh,,,
wander off this way,
♪
Oh!
Hey, it's
the Donna Reed show,
honey,
you could've phoned,
I thought I'd catch you
with another man,
oh, they left hours ago,
,,,if you don't start
coming around more often,
sit down, dear,
oh, not there,
the cat's been sick,
Bob show up?
Oh, sure,
I put him right to work,
he handles that harvester
like a real expert,
Bob's a good kid,
yeah, he seems to be,
you think it was smart
sending him to me?
After all, there's lots of
other places he could work,
well, I want you two to get
to know each other better,
it'll make it easier
when we have to tell him,
that he's an Android?
Oh, Russ,
why can't we bring things
out in the open?
All:Ll right!
And ruin the whole set‐up?
Oh, ceece, that's crazy!
Things might start
to get shaky as it is,
what do you mean?
Labor's so scarce
this season,
the other ranchers
are beginning to bellyache,,,
which is only natural
when they drive by my places
and see I've got
crews at work,
maybe it'd be only fair
to certify some prisoners
to them,
fair? Fair?!
I'm not interested
in what's fair,
I'm only interested in stuff
that makes my head look bigger,
he looks like dick Tracy,
in another 20 years,
he'll look like boss hogg,
I chucked in
a big wad of dough
to get you elected, too,
oh, no, this is my idea,
and I'm taking
the profits from it,
and you can't play
with my tinker toys, either,
who else in the valley's
got cotton pickers
at 75 cents a day?
Jolly green giant does,
there's gonna be
a lot of cotton
plowed under this year
for lack of help to pick it,
but not on my places,
I'll have a monopoly,
boardwalk, park place‐‐
think of it,
and I'm using the shoe,
,,,I'll be wealthy,
is he gonna sing now?
( Laughs )
Of course I meant "we",
of course,
but you'll be dead,
(huckles
I wish we could just
skip a year right now,
yep, so do I,
(niffs
you using denorex, honey?
I just pulled a big one,
I'm harvesting for yancey
and collingwood,
I take 60% as my share,
they're good farmers,
and they've got
a fat crop,
that goes to fill
your fat little cheeks,
where in the world
will you get enough hands?
Well, I know where
two of them are right now,
I like obstacles,
I know, I put enough
in your way,
yeah, you, uh‐‐
you sure played hard‐to‐get,
yeah, you let the phone
ring twice,
I wasn't, really,
nah, gotta shove,
bye‐bye,
oh, please stay
for dinner, Russ,
oh, I'm sorry, I can't,
at least a drink, then,
your favorite, loverboy,
cotton gin and tonic,
(aughs
what is it that's
so important this time?
The way things are going,
I sometimes think
we should break up,
gee, you mean it grandma?
What does uncle dad
have to say about that?
Don't ever say that,
don't even think it,
at least not until
the crop's in,
I may not show it
or say it,
but I need you,
I need you,
tooth inventory,
I'll stay for that drink,
we'll forget all about
business for a little while,
and just think
about genetics,
ohh,
boy, I hate this,
man, my eyebrows
look great over there
in the mirror, though,
57!
Enough with the bouncing
already!
‐ hi there, Jenny,
‐ oh, hi,
how's baby doing today?
Holding her own, I guess,
but she's asking
to call her "squeaky"ow,
gee, I don't know,
come people just can't take
this kind of hard work,
she was muttering
something about Ford
and dry‐clicking a toy gun,
but your honorable mom
didn't bother
to have a doctor
check any of us,
he's gonna start singing
you ain't gonna make
a cotton weigher out of me,
43!
Wait a minute,
this is a bag of rayon,
we'll make a cotton picker
out of you yet,
not on your
cotton‐pickin' life,
(aughs
funny,
wonder what she wanted,
40,
hey, who's the guy
in the cage?
That's my brother‐cousin,
he's likes sodey‐pop,
Well, at least
the bag is cotton,
we can get something
for that,
we were supposed to read?
I thought we were
sewing today,
(huckles
I wish I could get
a sitting‐down job,
why don't you call
a temp service?
‐ Igor, down!
‐ Igor! Mm!
With two heads,
you'd still be a moron,
would he be a two‐headed‐‐
♪
( Shouting )
Hiya, fuji! Ha ha!
Prison was never like this
when I was there,
huh?
Anyone not behaving
spends a night in the box step,
we're going to a party
at the county jail,
all:Eah!
That's the problem
with today's youth,
this is how their image
of prison is,
Hey, look at me,
I'm still stupid,
if anybody dances with me,
it's by accident,
hey, we gotta eat
on that table, get off,
oh, ask me about
my extra chromosome,
hey, I got a girl,
I got a girl!
Oh, how'd she find out
I was a geek?
Oh, well, ha ha ha!
Jerry lewis‐‐
geeky guy, denture wearer,
Whoops,
Hey, everybody, get me,
I'm doing the Abe Lincoln,
yeah!
Go, go, go!
( Chatter continues )
Gregory pick,
this week on solid gold,
Yeah, I planned it that way,
that's right,
I knew that,
no! It's Vic tayback!
( Music stops )
Oh, Mel!
Drop me here,
hey, man, that's my money
in there,
just a short
intermission, men,
I need two dishwashers
in the galley,
‐ I want two volunteers,
‐ ( All laugh )
All right, all right,
I'll take you and you,
whoa, I ain't no pearl‐diver,
that's not a requirement
for washing dishes,
I am a just man,
even a philosopher of pots,
possibly the most erudite bum
for miles around,
an actor of sorts,
but in this day
of crass materialism,
with dog‐eat‐dog
and man‐bite‐man,,,
come on, speed it up,
,,,the laborer
is worthy of his hire
and the artist of his due,
( indistinct )
What kind of gum‐beatin'
is that?
Such a wower,
as majordomo
of the kitchen,
and as field marshal
of the mess hall,,,
and whistle‐master of
the junior high Baton squad,,,
but I reiterate,
I am a just man,
and I claim that labor
is worth recompense,
your pay will be
pumpkin pie,
a whole one?
With whipped cream, man!
‐ then you got it made,
‐ this way, boys,
if only beatniks had just
stuck with pumpkin pie,
yeah, let's go,
‐ we should get out of here,
‐ suckers,
every segment ends with food
for some reason,
you know, I'm hungry,
what did you say
you were hungry for?
Um,,,
♪
The other day,
I was helping Joel
with a very
important project,
we were on
the satellite of love,
and, boy, if I wasn't there,
it really would've gone badly,
gypsy lies dormant,
her central nervous sim‐pack
temporarily shut down,
I'm helping Joel,
who's working tenaciously
with the skill
and cavalier quality
of a dermatologist
performing his 50th
routine face sanding,
‐ (hud
‐ uhh!
We were on
the satellite of love,
Joel:Nd it's aligned
by adjusting
the left horizontal gyro
and synchronizing
the output signal
with the feed input signal
on cambot's digital array
motherboard,
what are you doing?
Um, what are we
doing again, Tom servo?
We're linking gypsy's
cerebral data disk
to cambot's visual
output device
to take a look
at what she's thinking,
can I help?
No, last time you helped
on a project,
we had to jettison a whole
pan of burning rock candy
into deep space,
‐ can I watch?
‐ yeah, but just be careful
and don't touch anything,
I think I got this thing
all figured out,
let's hook it up
and see what happens,
input 3‐b,
okay, got it,
all right, it's all hooked up,
let's see how she looks,
let's turn on gypsy's
higher brain functions now,
‐ I'll do it,
‐ no, let me do it,
here, I'll get it,
cambot, just roll back
the entire contents of
gypsy's brain
and put it on
the main viewer,
‐ this won't take long,
‐ shh!
Well, this'll be
the first time
anyone has ever
been able to see
what a computer
is actually thinking,
‐ well, there it is,
‐ what is it?
Oh, it's an 8x10
of Richard basehart
‐ and some ram chips,
‐ oh, brother,
another great mystery
of the universe explained,
‐ well, it could
be worse,
‐ how?
It could've been Bob eubanks
she was dreaming about,
‐ true,
‐ hey, everybody!
Hi, girl, how you doin'?
I had a dream,
I know you had a dream,
and we were all in it, right?
No, none of you were there,
oh, boy,
oh, cambot, flash‐forward
out of this Turkey,
we actually saw what
you were thinking, gypsy,
hey, crow, buddy, come on,
what's wrong?
What are you doing?
Oh, I'm sorry,
I was daydreaming,
what did you say?
‐ (larm buzzing )
‐ I was just‐‐
we got movies!
(Creaming
♪
No big surprise
in gypsy, I guess,
yeah,
♪ dancin' at a party,,, ♪
Nice set,
yeah, nice radio, too,
oh, you,
hey, I didn't know
she could sing,
I still don't know
she can sing,
‐ (singing)
‐ (snapping)
Nice percussion section,
listen to that hi‐hat,
♪ now at 18,
ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ ooh‐ba‐la, baby,
he's my Joe ♪
love him so ♪
♪ ooh‐ba‐la, baby, never,
never, never let me go ♪
♪ he's got charm,
he's got class ♪
♪ and all the women,
oh, yes, yes, yes ♪
♪ ooh‐ba‐la, baby,
he's my Joe ♪
love him so ♪
It's a puppet show,
thank you,
♪ I love to love,
but just with Joe ♪
♪ when I'm with him,
we go, go, go ♪
♪ ooh‐ba‐la, baby,
he's my Joe,,, ♪
Oh, how many dishes
did they have to do?
A fork each?
They're fast,
♪ ooh‐ba‐la, baby ♪
‐ ♪ ooh‐ba‐la, baby ♪
‐ ♪ Joe, Joe, Joe ♪
♪ ooh‐ba‐la, baby ♪
♪ never, never, never
let me go ♪
♪ ooh‐ba‐la, baby ♪
♪ ooh‐ba‐la‐‐
ooh‐ba‐la, baby ♪
♪ love him so ♪
♪ ooh‐ba‐la, baby ♪
♪ never, never, never
let me go ♪
( Cheering )
16 weeks on star search,
they call her coffee,
'cause she grinds so fine,
hey, blondie, come here,
you have more than a modicum
of talent, my dear,
oh, you mean these?
Thanks very large,
it's a shame you started
heisting banks
at such a tender age
that got you
in this predicament,,,
(queaking
,,,to help
the talented young,
you know,
this gift of yours
should be brought
to the attention of
someone who can help you,
hef?
To wit, mr, tropp,
you know, my dear,
in this area,
there are many homes
equipped with a large
electronic box,
it's called a refrigerator,
but that has nothing
to do with my story,
,,,that so fascinate
the citizen
that they sit in front
of it for hours,,,
boy, somebody's gotta take
that guy out of the rain, huh?
Very perspicacious,
um, what does this
mr, tropp have to do with it?
Mr, tropp, my dear,
has a not inconsiderable
financial interest
in kahula city's,,,
all:Ahula city?
You know, a promise
is a vacuous thing
unless brought to a point,
I'll consult mr, tropp
on the intercom,,,
if he knows all this,
why is he still a cook?
A little electronic device
called a phone,
station chow
calling headquarters,
earth to cook,
mr, tropp, you may not
be aware of it,,,
that phone doesn't look
like it was made
for a human head,
especially not his head,
we haven't decided
if that's human or not,
get to the verb, pinky,
mr, tropp,
I'm surprised at you,
very surprised
that you didn't jump
at this opportunity,
I suggest, after she pays
her debt to society,
that you give her
a trial on your t, v, station,
I have nothing to do
with the programming, pinky,
I don't know
anything about it,
that hasn't stopped you
from farming,
look, I'm no judge
of singing,
sir, you have but to hear
her mellifluous tones
and see her beauty,,,
plural,
and you would no more
judge her
than you would a flower,
pretty articulate
for a slop cook,
the little blonde
with the sister?
Yeah,
oh, yeah,
sure, I'll listen to her,
send her up here
to the house,
thank you, mr, tropp,
thank you,
now, you go right up
to his house,
oh, thank you,
thank you, thank you,
if you are happy,
that is my reward,
and good luck,
what a gut,
what do you intend to do?
Do? Don't be square,
I'm going up there
and singing his ears out
right now,
wait a minute, kid,
let's talk this over,
yeah, think about it,
he'll probably give you
that corny pass about
becoming his "housekeeper",
the one you chomped on
like a bass?
Yeah, right out of
the cotton,
into a bed of thorns,
are you crazy?
No, I've got ambition,
that's all,
is that what you call it?
You're not going up there
to his house,
I certainly am,
but you heard
what lillibet said,
sour grapes,
she got tossed
out of the nest,
oh, and what are you?
The next candidate?
Don't be dirty‐minded,
oh, it's hard not to, mamie,
real hard,
and I don't think
mr, tropp's that kind,
oh, wow,
I can take care
of myself,
oh, yes, you can take care
of yourself,
never take help
from a guy named pinky,
that's your first mistake,
stop calling me "kid"!
I'm older than you,
and besides‐‐
yeah, in one way,
you were born before I was,
and?
Don't be a sucker,
the only way to get
a booking is‐‐
is through an agent
or a producer or somebody
like that,
yeah, dream on,
look, we serve out
our 30 days,
and then we go on to
Hollywood like we planned,
you listen!
Will you stop trying to
keep me under an umbrella?
I'm my own umbrella,
I'm gonna be way out
in front of those people,
and if mr, tropp can help me
get things started,
so much the better,
ah, you can trust me,
janey,
I'm not gonna make
any nasty bargains,
no matter what,
unless your name comes up,
oh, I trust you,
listen, you know that,
I trust your intentions,
but when a sharpie
gets to working on you,
you never see through him,
,,,all men are dear
little cub scouts,
well, that's what
you think I think,
well, you're not
interfering this time,
hmm, I wonder
what she wanted,
( groaning )
What was that rat food
we had for chow anyway?
Rat food,
life's a bowl of filth, man,
look into the face of death,
it's the only way, baby!
Sorry,
it's Napoleon,
I'll just, uh, put this fifth
under the seat here,
heh heh,
I love that,
Didn't get enough
in the chow line, eh, Bob?
I've been looking for these,
these are my mom's peaches,
Uh, you got a little,,,
something up there,
yeah, got it,
what's the matter, janey?
I'm in prison,
do you happen
to have a knife?
What for?
I might have to
stick it in somebody,
oh, now, that'd be a little
antisocial, wouldn't it?
Not where I come from,
penny went up
to the boss' house,
and she's still there,
and it doesn't take
an hour and a half
to sing a song,
maybe it's aida,
why don't you go up
and get her?
No, I can't,
penny and i‐‐
oh, forget it,
I forgot, you're on
the other side,
what other side?
The side of the judge
that sent us up here,
Sauron's dark army?
,,, happens to be your mom,
okay, like you said,
let's forget it,
well,,,don't get me wrong,
penny's okay,
she's just‐‐
well, she's just
a sucker for a line,
oh, really?
Look, couldn't you maybe
go up there
and pretend to want
to see mr, tropp?
Well,,,not very well,
not without some reason,
you see,
I'm a method actor,
but I think I have one,
‐ oh, good,
‐ on one condition,
you push me around
in a wheelbarrow
dressed as a spartan,
that you don't go jumping
to any conclusions
about what side I'm on,
it's a deal,
oh, thanks,
and you can't be
that naive, penny,
I just don't believe you,
after all,
I didn't send for you,
I didn't offer
to hear you sing,
you came up here
of your own free will,
you promoted yourself
with pinky to have him call‐‐
‐ no! He offered,
‐ I haven't finished,
but you came,
and I heard you,
and I promise to phone
my station manager
in the morning,
I'm very grateful,
mr, tropp,
but that's
not enough, penny,
there's still
that wheelbarrow thing,
,,, right now,
life is a matter
of horse trading,
there's whinnies and losers,
,,, favors for favors,
‐ (dogs growling)
‐ (knock on door)
Puff! Nowball! Down!
Oh, those are my hormones,
that'll be the pizza
I ordered,
Uh, I'm sorry to
bother you so late, mr,‐‐
yes, it's late,
that's what I said,
even though you're
a paid hand
living with the foreman,
these dogs
wouldn't know that,
well, what if we
told them?
Landis tell you about
that girl on his crew?
What girl?
I don't know her name,
they just call her "baby",
what about her?
She almost passed out
in the field,
she looks pretty sick,
she might have a bad heart,
yeah, yeah, I'll have her heart
replaced in the morning,
I'll just be out here
if you need me!
( Piano music playing )
Where is that piano?
Now, I, uh,,,
know you two love
the rich taste
of field hands,
so here's a little
snacky‐poo for you,
all right, go,
( barking )
Hey, save me a wing!
( Penny screaming )
Good thing I left
my dog‐beater over here,
( screaming continues )
Take them away!
Mamie, calm down,
dogs can't climb ladders,
here!
Boy, to think
she jumped up there,
,,,the dogs don't like it,
kind of dangerous,
isn't it, mr, kropp‐‐
letting those dogs
run around loose?
Come on,
you were trying
to run away, were you?
That's a lie,
they chased me up there,
get to your quarters,
I suppose they ate
your homework, too,
uh, should I get
your chin wax, sir?
That guy was sneaking around
down behind the kitchen,
checking at tin cans
to see what kind of food
you're feeding them,
what business is it of his?
Maybe he's a nutritionist,
yeah,
♪
Your sister says you're
really a sucker for a line,
‐ I got away from him,
‐ you mean you had to?
He doesn't waste
much time, does he?
So he set the dogs on me,
what? I'll kill him,
so help me‐‐
now, wait a minute,
that won't do any good,
nobody'll be able
to help you then,
especially not him,
he'll be dead,
(aughs
see? He'll kill him,
♪
( Chattering )
Oh, wow,
you know, it's a lot easier
if you took the guitar off,
at least once,
you can't dance,
you're the band,
get back here,
How much?
Nine bucks,
what are you, hans brinker
all of a sudden?
You want 'em or not?
You go buy them
there, then,
fat chance,
I gotta have 'em,
charge it, buster,
don't forget‐‐
you don't leave the ranch
until you're paid up,
even if you're time's up,
and I thought Lincoln
got rid of slavery,
yeah, he's right over there
working on it,
getting rid of slavery,
yeah, really groovy, man,
I don't like you,
‐ (music stops)
‐ all right, closing time,
‐ everybody out,
‐ (all booing)
No dancing,
that's not the potty,
them boys is awful quiet,
Greg, don't do it!
Ow!
That'll teach you,
don't mess with the light,
hey, Greg's got
child‐bearing hips,
eek!
He's used to
living with boys,
chicken,
honey, when I do a strip,
I get paid for it,
( laughter )
Oh, Russ, you're wonderful,
thanks, grandma,
between this moon
and you, I,,,
don't know which one
is which,
wear a necktie next time
so I'll know who's you,
about bob‐‐
he's been working
a week now,
and there's a couple of
things that I've noticed,
he works hard, he's good
on that harvester, too,
it's a tricky machine,
and I like Bob,
a lot,
I knew you would,
everybody does,
but look, we both can't have
a hole in our heads,
that would make us
bowling balls,
do we have to talk
about this now?
That's one of the reasons‐‐
one of the things that‐‐
look, that has got
to be settled,
what you mean is, you wanted
to talk about Bob,
well, I'm using you
to get to him,
no, baby, of course not,
I wanted to have
some time with you alone,
look, believe me, kitten,
I'm thinking about you,
but Bob's no kid,
he's inquisitive,
he's been around,
he could've figured out
our set‐up,
set‐up?
Don't use that term, Russ,
that's a gangster's term,
what we're doing
is absolutely legal,
except for the parts
that aren't,
but your boy, my dear,
is a do‐gooder,
don't be a don't‐be,
,,, he comprehends
this set‐up‐‐
the situation, I mean‐‐
he's liable to hate you,
now, I'm thinking
of you, kitten,
he's your boy,
you asked me
to put him to work,
and I wouldn't fire him
for the world,
but I don't want him
to end up hating you,
kill him, he's evil
and must be destroyed,
I think you're right, Russ,
I think it would be better
if Bob were,,,
put to sleep?
If he had other interests,
oh, nothing matters
but you,,,
and us, together,
all three of us,
oh, kiss me,
I can't go on this way,
my lunch is coming‐‐ooh!
Wow, some boys
just have bikes,
reaper man,
watch modern technology
rip through this field
of teenage gals,
it's reaper madness,
hey, you just harvested
his sister,
you look all beat,
not beets, cotton,
you just fall off
a turnip truck or something?
I didn't mean for you
to drink it, you silly woman,
it's kerosene,
funny, huh?
Oh, good, I thought maybe
that crocodile tropp got her,
oh, you don't seem worried
about him getting me,
I don't have to worry
about you,
you can take care
of yourself,,,
you little wildcat,
you little buffalo,
thanks, Bob,
you're real gone,
well, thanks,
I'm no expert,
but I'm pretty sure
I'm still here,
yeah, you're‐‐
you're real gone yourself,
they're both gone,
they left,
Medic!
Combine got another one,
Better get this girl
to a doctor,
are you bossing this crew?
No, you are, wino,
uh, the name is Dave,
Dave wino,
what are you doing?
I'm taking her to a doctor
in your truck,
not in any company car,
you ain't,
get back to your
muscatel, creep,
hey, it's mogen David,
and don't call me creep,
hey, you want a spritzer?
Stamp all foremen
dead out,
well, now everybody's gone,
Oh, it's the purina
test kitchens,
Well, I pulled her teeth,
is that what you wanted?
I'm sorry, I have some
very bad news for you,
I'm not a real doctor,
she works on
the same ranch I do,
oh,
well, the girl
was five months pregnant,
she died of
a severe hemorrhage
after a miscarriage,
must've started while
you were bringing her here,
gee, I'm sorry we even
made fun of this movie,
she was lying
in the truck, moaning,
five months pregnant,
ah, the poor kid,
well, we did
everything we could,
we were just too late,
and we're not real doctors,
you mind giving miss duff
the information
for the death certificate,
you know,,,i didn't
even know her name,
"baby" is all
we ever called her,
she worked as a cotton picker
for mr, tropp
out in welling Springs,
hey, you got nothing
to explain to me, pal,
,,, we'll get in touch
with him,
is there anything else
I can do?
No,,,
get off my counter,
,,,then find out what
the family wants to do,
well, thank you, uh,,,
for everything you've done,
or didn't do,
wonder what he wanted,
♪
Meanwhile,
at stately Wayne manor,,,
and she was
five months pregnant,
she was just
a kid herself,
"baby", we called her,
nobody even knew her name,
that's the worst part
about it,
she‐‐she dies
in a strange place
without friends or anybody,
and nobody
even knows her name,
she should've died
at cheers,
then everyone would've
known her name,
if only I had known,
well, why didn't you?
Why didn't somebody?
Mr, tropp is supposed
to see that everyone
has a medical exam
before they're sent
into the field,
he does it himself,
well, it was part
of the agreement,
uh, I mean, our,,,
illegal contract,
I don't care
about the law,
not after I tell you
a few of the things
that are going on
out at mr, tropp's
private little kingdom,
wheelbarrows everywhere,
look, you're a judge,
I'll be the judge of that,
suppose I came before you,
do you think you'd be
doing me a favor
by sending me out
to this ranch?
No, I go because
I've got to,
I live in a shack,
I sleep on a canvas cot,
there are four washbasins
and two showers
for twenty guys,
which is great,
and that healthy food‐‐
that I'm paying for‐‐
do you know what I found out
about that food?
Tropp's feeding
canned dog food,
and he calls it
beef stew,
oh, no!
Not canned,
it should be dry,
that's part
of the agreement,
he's doing it,
mother, I saw the empty cans,
I guess you didn't know
this was going on, did you?
No, and maybe
mr, tropp doesn't,
oh, he knows every move
that's made,
well, Bob, it's‐‐
it's, uh‐‐
it's just that,,,
Russ is very ambitious,
when did you start
calling him Russ?
Got a bunch of people
assigned to him
on your orders,
he gets them
for six bits a day
and feeds them slop,
it's not slop,
it's science diet,
and it's very expensive,
young man,
she's no more a vagrant
than you are,
and she could tell you
a couple of things
that'd open your eyes
about how it is to be
under the thumb of a guy
like this tropp,
whoooo!
I can't help myself,
no, but you can stop
sentencing people
to his ranch,
mother, don't take
my word for it,
have the sheriff
make an investigation,
tell the editor
of the newspaper,,,
sing it from
the mountaintops!
What did you say?
You can't help yourself?
I'm in love
with Russ tropp,
mom, "love"s
a pretty big word,
he's my husband,
"husband" is a pretty
big word, too,
what did you say?
We were married
four months ago,
wait, so you're my grandma?
My sister? Y mom?
Did you marry bill Wyman?
You never told anybody,
I guess,
you don't even
live together,
mother, that‐‐
that isn't like you,
you've‐‐you've never
been sneaky,
( sobbing )
It must've been his idea,,,
you're learning,
keep it up, aunt mom,
oh, mother, i'm‐‐
I'm so sorry for you,
don't be,
please don't think of me
like that,
but now I'm starting
to like you,
,,,things will work out
all right,
sure, just keep
telling yourself that,
and Russ has lots of
good qualities,
truth is, mom,
you've been taken
for one long, hard ride,
I'm sure he has, to you,
I just haven't been able
to find any,
I was hoping you and Russ
would hit it off,
well, he did punch me once,
(huckles
Bob,,,
you said something
when you first came home
about wanting to go
up to Montana,
oh, you mean that thing
about Montana?
Maybe that would be better
for now,
we'll, uh‐‐
they look like
an evolution chart,
well, thank you, mom,
I'll pay my own way,
that would be fair,
mom, could you
make me a sandwich?
Good luck, mother,
oh, man, I'm not
getting paid enough,
Bob!
Love me!
Jim,
love me,
I want you to,,,
yeah? Anything I can
help you with in here, ma'am?
I'm gonna send you
on an errand,
up to mount pilot?
Okay, I'll go get
my one bullet,
Hey, Greg Brady's
leading the group,
yeah,
what's the idea taking
that girl off this place
without permission?
I don't know,
something to do,
‐ she's dead,
‐ oh!
Well, when can she
be back on the job?
What do you expect me
to do, break up?
She was gonna have a baby,
I didn't know
she was pregnant,
no, but you knew
something was wrong,
I warned you,
the fields
killed her, Mac,
hey, call me "big Mac",
you're not kidding,
it's the last word,
I'm checkin' off
the place,
no, that was
the last word,
hiya, Greg,
hi, Jenny,
hi, other girl,
they didn't caulk
that float very well,
I heard what you said,
that's awful about baby,
she didn't even
have a chance,
why couldn't she have said
something to somebody?
I don't know, Jenny,
maybe she was,,,
rock stupid,
hey, Joel, I was
kind of wondering‐‐
what does real cotton
feel like?
Oh, I can show you
what that is,
hey, gypsy, come on
into the theater,
gypsy?
Oh!
Hey, gypsy? Look up
at the screen,
remember when they
showed the cotton?
Use your teledyne vector
to figure it out,
will you reproduce
some cotton for us?
(Roaning)
‐ okay, uhh,
‐ oh, gross,
it's not done yet, Joel,
gypsy, will you
run up to the‐‐
to the main ship
and make some new‐‐
make a new batch for us?
Just put it on
the main table there,
(roans
it's like fluffy pudding,
yeeh!
Probably back home
to du quoin,
I'd like to see you again,
lots of times,
and then stop abruptly,
breaking your heart
like a toy,
this stuff smells, Joel,
Mmm, mmm,
mmm, mmm,
tastes like juicy fruit,
and pizza,
I'm not worried
about that,
you'll never get lost,
only if you have
a compass and a dream,
you know how before
you said about,,,
you being stuck her
and that I'm trying
to run away?
Well, I'm not leaving,
I'm gonna stay,
and then stay some more,
tropp will have to
throw me off the place,
I'm gonna stay,
and I'm gonna look after you,
and I'm gonna take care
of that guy tropp, too,
and then I'm gonna replant
the whole forest, Ben,
see, he's greedy,
he's gonna spill himself,
and when does,
I'll nail him,
so help me,
I'll nail him to the wall,
oh, use drywall screws,
they're much better,
janey!
Oh, we'd better
get out of here,
hey, look at that,
that's some trailer,
I'll bet that cotton's
finished, too, up there,
Oh, gypsy, honey,
look at this,
you are sick,
aren't you?
Oh, my good‐‐oh,
hey, Joel, this is great,
this is great, cowabunga!
I feel like Rosemary Clooney
in white Christmas,
having a little trouble
with that gypsy unit, huh?
Yeah, it's something
with her off switch, I think,
I can't get it to stop
being on,
♪ well, the weather
outside is frightful ♪
Hey! His is great!
♪ the weather outside,,, ♪
I think you should have her
fabricate something less messy,
like, uh, salt water Taffy,
oh, I don't think that‐‐
‐ yeah!
‐ that's just great, Tom,
that's just great,
I've got a sick robot
on my hands,
and all you do is give me
more stupid commands
to deal with,
we've got a mess,
maybe she should bring up
some paper towels!
(Roans
this is great! Eah!
Tom, that's it,
get out,
‐ I'm just
having some fun,
‐ out!
Can't take advantage
of a robot anymore?
Would you get out of here?
‐ stupid human,
‐ get out!
Gypsy, make another
Tom servo!
‐ leave me alone!
‐ (roans
happy birthday!
Hey, I feel like
Rosemary Clooney,
Joel, crow, how are you?
Get out of here,
I don't care
if you're a second‐generation
Tom servo, get out!
Did you notice there was
a commercial sign there?
‐ I gotta go,
‐ oh, that's great,
we got a commercial sign,
♪
I'm sorry, Tom,
but that other Tom
is gonna have to be
destroyed,
well, you didn't have to‐‐
I needed a friend,
you didn't have
to dismantle him,
crow, come on,
get out here,
cut that out,
crow!
Sorry,
nice, cold,
dribbling water,
but Bob didn't tell you
everything,
the rankest thing of all‐‐
about the boss
and girls,
you mean Angelo?
No, I mean the boss‐‐
that tropp,
boy, is he rank,
do you know what you're
saying, young lady? Do you?
Did I stutter or something,
grandma?
,,,you spreading
malicious gossip,
malicious truth,
‐ proof of what?
‐ ask my sister penny,
he got her up to his house
and was gonna get her on t, v,
and then he tried
to make a pass at her,
but she fumbled
on the fourth down,
go on,
then there was more
bad stuff, real bad,
,,, his housekeeper,
living at the house
with him,
that's one way of getting out
of picking cotton,
and what a way,
got it!
Damn roaches,
what did I do?
What did I say?
It's nothing
that you did,
you come along with me,
♪
Oh, wow,
another musical number,
hot damn,
they all sound the same,
I think she's gonna
incite a riot,
someone get some
animal tranquilizers,
♪ ,,,as a salamander ♪
♪ slip and slide away,,, ♪
Well, you know,
maybe that dog food
is good for them,
she's really got
a shiny coat,
it's a high‐pro‐glow,
♪ jiggle and wriggle
and rock ♪
♪ jiggle and wiggle
and wriggle and rock ♪
She's just reading
the stage directions,
nice lighting,
♪ oh, jiggle and wiggle
and wriggle and rock ♪
♪ I don't want you today ♪
She's the one who caused
all that trouble at attica,
( cheering )
Yikes!
♪ ,,,you're my desire ♪
♪ but you should
be told,,, ♪
‐ I'm in love,
‐ duck!
She's got a really
neat body,
♪ but you're as slimy,
baby, as a salamander ♪
♪ slip and slide away ♪
Why am I here, you guys?
This guys validated
my existence, heh heh!
She uses more peroxide
in her hair
than an entire mash unit,
♪ salamander ♪
♪ mander, mander,
salamander ♪
♪ slip and slide away ♪
Oh, thanks,
♪ mander, salamander,,, ♪
This is like the Las Vegas
prison camp, I think,
las vegan,
♪ I don't want you today ♪
♪ I don't want you,,, ♪
Another example
of great lighting,
(ndistinct )
Pow, pow, pow,
all right, that's lunch,
everybody,
it's the deli tray,
try and look smart,
okay, let's‐‐
I said look smart,
penny?
Oh, excuse me, kids,
come on, kids, let's go!
♪
Another one,
where's janey? I've been
looking all over for her,
oh, we sold her into slavery
for some magic beans, why?
Then she got in a car
with him, and they drove off,
they went off the ranch?
Sure, out into the highway
and toward kahula city,
who was he?
He had on a suntan uniform,
you mean he was naked?
,,, and Angelo let janey go,
oh,
oh? What?
I think I know,
come on, penny,
all: I know a wiener man,
he owns a hot dog stand ♪
What do you intend to do,
judge Steele?
And who are all these guys
on the floor?
,,,clean up a mess for which
I'm partly responsible,
I'm sorry,
you're sorry?
I'm stepping on cameramen
left and right
in this shot,
I asked you for the truth,
I think you gave it to me,
I just didn't think
it was going to be so,,,
hard to take,
and I had no idea
the steering wheel
would be this big,
hey, that guy's great,
oh, it's Greg Brady again,
we like him,
♪ you can make me cry,
you can shake the stars ♪
♪ right out of the sky,,, ♪
One for servo,
she's doing a cover
of that other guy's song,
you think I look good?
I do,
yeah, you could make
a good whiskey decanter,
it's because of my b, v, d,'s,
9:30, get those people
turned in,
fluffy, crotch, bad,
here comes sheriff Taylor,
that's the sheriff's car,
how can you tell?
The car they took janey
away in‐‐was it marked?
I don't think so,
I don't remember,
I'm gonna check into this,
all right, everybody,
turn in,
‐ you'd better
go turn in,
‐ no,
turn into what?
(Aughter
(kissing noises )
Okay, so tell me something,
and be honest,
do I really look
like colonel Tom Parker?
(Issing noises )
Wait here, penny,
filmed in america's
tractor pavilion,
scenic Wisconsin,
that's a really tall tractor,
quick, hop behind
the manure‐spreader,
that's it,
(niffs
yuck!
That's the man?
Yeah, but he only
speaks Spanish,
so much the better,
I'm so sorry,
he's from Barcelona,
who's the greaser behind
the manure‐spreader?
Looks like James Dean,
looks more like Jimmy Dean,
rebel without a sausage,
( Indistinct chatter )
Go get Margarita,
and hurry,
frozen or on the rocks?
♪
Penny, you stay here
and warn us if anyone comes,
come on, Margarita,
I love that man,
( man speaking Spanish )
What is he saying?
He mumbled something
about shooting the kid
behind the tractor,
but I couldn't
make out the rest,
( Spanish chatter
continues )
It's a fajita recipe,
sizzle, sizzle, sizzle,
( Spanish chatter
continues )
"Migration permits,,,
to work,"
okay, good,
now let's move on
to the chapter
on making friends,
( Spanish chatter
continues )
Okay,
( Clatter )
Oh, sorry about
the garbage can,
we'll just be going,
posh, puff, sic,
really mess up
the savages,
go, boys,
let's get out of here!
( Barking )
( Screaming )
Have you had your teeth
cleaned, little fella?
Big tartar build‐up there,
oh, they're just mad
'cause those humans
got to eat
all their dog food,
Joan Collins,
Cut! Okay, that's a wrap,
get the dog off,
okay, nice scene, everyone,
let's get home,
we've got another scene
to do in the morning,
that wasn't in the script,
it is now,
they're really embellishing
here, aren't hey?
( Spanish chatter )
She's lying,
he's not her lover,
he's a fighter,
Sit,
me or the dogs?
When you take morales
over the border,
take these kids
along with you,
and get rid of them
down there,
wait, Russ,
that's going too far!
You want us to end up
in the federal clink?
This is no time to argue,
mr, maytag man,
,,,you won't have to get
your hands dirty,
you go along, too,
(verlapping chatter )
What's the meaning of this?
It's a big
production number,
get them in the car,
I'll handle these monkeys,
looks like there
could be a Rumble,
( dogs growling )
This is a mutiny, a riot,
now, go on back
to your quarters,
or you'll find yourselves
back in jail,
we'll take the jail,
you set your dogs
on two of our people,
mr, tropp,
we don't like that,
look, boss, I like hounds
as well as anybody,
but those dogs are killers,
if I wasn't sure
Greg Brady was a guy,
‐ i'd, uh‐‐
‐ snap out of it,
( growling )
Drive through 'em!
Run 'em down!
Oh, great,
finally, a good job,
it's the cast
from a tobe hooper film,
little punk hit me
with a nerf ball!
Come on, officer krupke,
you want a riot?
I'll give you a riot,
all:Rr!
Get to bed before
somebody gets killed!
That'll be enough of that,
Mitch bowers!
What do you want,
aunt bea?
And so, Manuel noriega
quickly seizes the opportunity
to make his escape,
That ought to hold 'em,
right in the nunzio,
Hold him, hold him!
Grab him, grab him!
Hold him!
Give him a wedgie, yeah,
I certainly am glad
you're here, judge Steele,
there's been a mutiny,
a riot,,,
a coup,
what's this all about, Bob?
This guy's a coyote,
he's bringing 300 wetbacks
from over the border
on tropp's orders,
get some towels,
nice to see you,
but, as you can see,
there's been a riot‐‐
search him, Mitch,
( all chattering )
They all want to search him,
yeah, man,
Wait a minute,
these are stills
from yards of leather,
take them into custody,
( all agreeing )
Do your duty!
To god and your country,
obey the law of the pack,
I've just learned tonight
of some of the conditions
you've been living under,
I read your contract,
I can't believe
you're working for this,
,,, so does the county
have an obligation
to pay to you
as prisoners,
I'm gonna have you all
into court
in the morning,
if it's the last thing
I do as a judge,
it will be to commute
your sentences
to time served,
then we're gonna do a show,
and that will be the last
thing I do as a judge,
'cause I just got a reading
for murder, she wrote,
I think we might need
a few temporary deputies,
Bob,,,
find some for me,
,,, and you and you,
and scarecrow
and the rest of you,
man, oh, man,
this is wild, ha ha!
( Laughter )
♪
This is what deputies do?
I think so,
only they're usually parked
at a mister donut
doing it,
hey, m, t, v,
Mexican television, heh!
David byrne's new band,
♪ go, calypso, go ♪
♪ sing the chorus ♪
♪ everybody thinks
the calypso song,,, ♪
Mamie made it!
Auntie mamie!
♪ Trinidad's been had ♪
( Indistinct lyrics )
♪ Hello, boys, if I'd known
you were coming ♪
♪ I'd have baked
a rum cake ♪
I can't believe
I'm putting up with this,
♪ go, calypso, go ♪
♪ everybody, go ♪
She's got neat underwear
in this one,
nice diapers,
they're huggies, all right,
this must be the theme song
of the cousteau society,
‐ ♪ New York? ♪
‐ ♪ yes, New York ♪
And so we leave the cave
of the giant barracuda,
(aughter
as we so end the film,
we are reminded
of our tiny friends
of mamie Van doren,
‐ how was that?
‐ great,
‐ close?
‐ yeah,
good Gregory peck,
that was my Chinese gangster
impression,
♪ go, calypso, go ♪
This is probably the longest
minute in film history,
do you realize that?
You don't have to look
up her skirt, it's open,
♪ shake the banana ♪
♪ come on, boys,
and carry my bananas ♪
What in the world
does that mean?
"Carry my bananas"?
‐ I don't want to know,
‐ it's a metaphor,
♪ everybody, go ♪
♪ go, calypso, go ♪
Hey, lookit,
♪ sing the chorus ♪
( Indistinct lyrics )
So that's what
the Tijuana brass is doing,
♪ I don't take jokers,
he don't go ♪
♪ tell us, girl,
why you shake the hips so ♪
She looks so Latin, too,
so do they,
♪ I take the money ♪
♪ I get the tickles ♪
Huh?
You wouldn't know that
to look at her,
♪ mama go calypso ♪
♪ baby go calypso ♪
Everyone calypso,
♪ everyone calypso ♪
I feel like i'm
in the tiki room,
I wish I were,
you got the profile for it,
thank you,
hello there!
Well, there she is,
folks,,,
your pants are on fire, oh,
you know,,,
(Turns sound off)
My sentiments exactly,
oops,
,,,being up there
with penny,
the applause and all?
Oh, I'd miss you
much, much more,
than what? Rison?
Well, we're both gone,
you know,
Bob, the foreman wants you
at the "q" ranch,
something about
one of the machines,
okay,
and he wants to
run you over with it,
can't I go with you?
You'd better say that,
you can't start too early
if you're gonna
be a cotton‐pickin'
rancher's wife,
hey, watch your mouth, pal,
I guess we'd best
be going, too, huh?
Yeah, let's get real gone,
let's mosey, daddy‐o,
♪ go, go, go, calypso, go ♪
♪ go, the calypso, go ♪
(Knock on door )
Come on in,
hey, Joel, I hope we're
not interrupting anything,
not at all,
can I get you some ram chips
or something?
Oh, no, just ate,
yeah, stuffed,
couldn't eat another bite,
okay, well,
what can I do you for?
Well, we were down
in the galley,
playing freeze tag,
and we started wondering
about that goofy mutant
Charlie callas guy in the film,
you know,
that bespectacled weenie
that no one would dance with,
what's the story on him?
Right, I think I know
what you mean,
cambot, could you put up
frame 2,325?
I think it's somewhere
around there,
let's check it out,
yeah, that's the guy,
look at him,
poor sap,
probably has a family,
so, Joel, what's the point
of having this guy in the film?
What's his purpose?
I thought you might
want to know,
so I got us all
goofy hats to wear,
everybody gets one,
and you get this one,
and I got myself
some glasses,
you guys can't
wear glasses
'cause you don't really
have eyes to speak of,
and then the goofy friend
is the guy who wears his hat
sideways like this
and always gets killed first
in the haunted house,
like, "guys? Uys?
Hey, this isn't funny
anymore, guys?"
Oh, so it's, like,,,
"guys? Uys?"
"Hey, come on,"
"guys?"
All:Aaah!
‐ yeah, you got it,
‐ cool,
hey, Joel,
this is kind of fun,
yeah, okay,
so, like,
what else does he do?
What's his point, though?
Well, the goofy guy
is around
to irritate the audience
so they build up
a real lot of resentment,
so nobody's hurt
when he gets offed,
‐ ahh,
‐ yeah,
now, let's end up
with the goofy dance, okay?
Yeah, that's‐‐
that's pretty good,
you're catching on,
anyway, I thought‐‐
it's almost time
for the experiment
to get done with,
and I thought maybe we could
do some letters, okay?
All right, let's see here,
let's see,
this one is from Cheryl Watson
in shreveport, Louisiana,
and she says‐‐
cambot, can you put it
up on the screen?
"To the man
and the two robots,
I love your show,
"I came home
one Saturday night
"and tuned on the t, v,‐‐
turned on the t, v,
"I had no idea what
I was watching,
"but it was hilarious,
so I didn't care,
"normally I watch
Saturday night live
on Saturday,
but now I watch
m, s, t, 3000,"
live, from space,
it's us!
Right, anyway,
we got one more here,
and, cambot, you want
to put this one up
on the screen there?
Oh, this one is from
a woman named Dee,
it says, "dear Joel,
servo and crow,
"greetings, guys,
"Joel, you are
one talented human,
and I'm glad you decided
to give crow and servo
free will,"
well, thanks for noticing,
"and, crow, servo,
I love you, little bots,
"keep on doing
those group parodies
of those moldy,
oldie movies, okay?"
I love you little bot, too,
"stoke of genius,"
and that's from a woman
named wee,
"love, wee,"
that's us, I think,
I think it's us,
anyway, so, cambot,
why don't we put up
the information
of the information club?
Tom servo, you want to
give them our address?
That's right, it's,,,
Be the smartest guy
on your block,
have the biggest brain
on your block
by becoming a member
of the m, s, t, 3000
information club,
anyway, that's the end
of the experiment, sirs,
what do you think?
You know, I think
we should keep
the mamie Van doren films
to ourselves,
and I think
you should file this,
until next time,
double‐stuff,
♪